leela.tv 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy

It is important to Leela TV to help its users retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the site has to offer. We'll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, Leela TV follows various principles in accordance with standard practices for user privacy and data protection.

We won't sell or give away your name, mail address, email address, phone number or any other information to anyone, unless required by law.

We'll use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your submitted data from unauthorised access.

NOTICE

We'll ask for information ,when we need , that personally identifies you (personal information) and allows us to contact you, if needed. Generally, this information is requested when you create a Registration ID on the site, or when you subscribe to a News Letter, enter a contest , fill up various forms, participate in surveys or polls, or for example, join a premium or Age Restricted section of the site. We use your personal information primarily for purposes stated below:  
 To makev the site easier for you to use by not having to provide us with information more than once.  
 To help you find and consume contents of your choice, which otherwise not available to an unregistered user.  
 To help us create content most relevant to you.  
 To alert you to site upgrades, changes in policies or information, special offers and other newv services Leela TV has in the offerings.

CONSENT

If you choose not to register or provide us with personal information, you can still use most of Leela TV. But, you'll not be able to access areas or act upon that require registration.

ACCESS

We'll provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may update these personal information when needed by logging into your Member Area. If you face any difficulty regarding updating your personal information, please contact: [[email protected]](http://www.leela.tv/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  \- you'll get a prompt response from us.

SECURITY

Leela TV has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honoured. We take necessary precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorised access, or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.  
Your personal information is never shared outside Leela TV without your prior permission, except under condition stated above. With Leela TV, data is stored in password-protected servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the countries where Leela TV has got its servers, or where Leela TV, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.Meanwhile, you have a significant role in protecting your information. 'No one' can see or edit your personal information without knowing your user name and password; you are not supposed to share your Log in credentials with others.

INFORMATION COLLECTED

There are two types of information that 'we' (Leela TV and its third party service providers) collect:  
 DIRECT INFORMATION. These are the information that you provide us with: typically during the registration, subscription and participation process. These may include your personal and financial transaction details.  
 FETCHED INFORMATION. These are the information we collect from your use ofv Leela TV and its associated third party services. This information may include:  
 Device-specific information. We may collect these information, such as, your hardware models, operating system, unique device identifiers and other.  
User Log. While you use ourq services or consume contents provided by Leela TV or supported external sites on Leela TV, we may automatically collect and store certain information in the server logs. This may include details of how you use our service, such as your search queries, contents consumed and internet protocol address. This also may include cookies that are able to uniquely identify your browser and/or your Leela TV account.  
Local Storage. We may collect and store information locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage, application data caches and other.  
 Anonymous Identifiers and Cookies.q Leela TV and its third party service providers - Google Analytics, video hosting services, CDN services, AD Networks, for example, may use various and changing technologies including anonymous identifiers and cookies to collect and store information on your device when you use Leela TV.

USES OF INFORMATION

In general words, we use the information that we collect and may store, to improve the overall user experience - to provide, maintain and develop services and products. This information is also used to protect Leela TV and its users.  
Leela TV will disclose your personal information, direct and/or fetched, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) comply to the edict to the law or comply with legal process served on Leela TV or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights and property of Leela TV and its family of websites and businesses, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Leela TV, its websites and businesses, or the public.

ENFORCEMENT

If some reason you believe, Leela TV has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by email at: [[email protected]](http://www.leela.tv/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) , and we'll determine and correct the problem, if there is any, promptly.

APPLICATION

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by Leela TV and its affiliates including services offered on other Leela TV websites such asLeela AD Network.  
Our Privacy Policy, however, doesn't apply to services offered by other companies or individuals including products and websites that may appear on Leela TV in your search results, or other.

 PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

Our Privacy Policy may change anytime, without prior notice. However, without your explicit consent, we'll not degrade your rights. We'll publish the updated version on this page and keep the prior version for your reference.
